{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"left ventricle and posterior wall of the right ventricle.",
					"right atrium and posterior wall of the right ventricle.",
					"right ventricle and inferior wall of the left ventricle.",
					"left ventricle and inferior wall of the right atrium."
				],
				"question": "The right coronary artery supplies blood to the:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "right ventricle and inferior wall of the left ventricle."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"on the lower abdomen.",
					"on either side of the chest.",
					"on the thighs or ankles.",
					"anywhere on the arms."
				],
				"question": "When preparing to obtain a 12-lead ECG, the LL and RL electrodes should be placed:",
				"source": "See Cardiac Monitoring"
			},
			"back": "on the thighs or ankles."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"causes an increase in the heart rate.",
					"prepares the body to handle stress.",
					"slows the heart and respiratory rates.",
					"dilates the blood vessels in the muscles."
				],
				"question": "In contrast to the sympathetic nervous system, the parasympathetic nervous system:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "slows the heart and respiratory rates."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"assess the scene for potential hazards.",
					"gain immediate access to the patient.",
					"determine if you need additional help.",
					"request a paramedic unit for assistance."
				],
				"question": "Upon arriving at the residence of a patient with a possible cardiac problem, it is MOST important to:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "assess the scene for potential hazards."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Labored breathing",
					"Flat jugular veins",
					"Dependent edema",
					"Pulmonary edema"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following signs is commonly observed in patients with right-sided heart failure?",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "Dependent edema"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"atrioventricular node.",
					"coronary sinus.",
					"sinoatrial node.",
					"bundle of His."
				],
				"question": "The electrical impulse generated by the heart originates in the:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "coronary sinus."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"left atrium.",
					"right ventricle.",
					"right atrium.",
					"left ventricle."
				],
				"question": "Deoxygenated blood from the body returns to the:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "right atrium."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"document his or her own perception.",
					"underline the patient’s quotes.",
					"use the patient’s own words.",
					"use medical terminology."
				],
				"question": "When documenting a patient’s description of his or her chest pain or discomfort, the EMT should:",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "use the patient’s own words."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"the inner layers of the aorta become separated.",
					"a weakened area develops in the aortic wall.",
					"all layers of the aorta suddenly contract.",
					"the aorta ruptures, resulting in profound bleeding."
				],
				"question": "A dissecting aortic aneurysm occurs when:",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "the inner layers of the aorta become separated."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"decreased pumping force of the heart muscle.",
					"widespread dilation of the systemic vasculature.",
					"a profound increase in the patient’s heart rate.",
					"hypovolemia secondary to severe vomiting."
				],
				"question": "Cardiogenic shock following AMI is caused by:",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "decreased pumping force of the heart muscle."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Metoprolol (Toprol)",
					"Aspirin",
					"Oxygen",
					"Furosemide (Lasix)"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following medications is commonly given to patients with chest pain to prevent blood clots from forming or getting bigger?",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care for Chest Pain or Discomfort"
			},
			"back": "Aspirin"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"it delivers prompt defibrillation to patients with ventricular fibrillation.",
					"it is lightweight, easy to use, and safe for the EMT who is using it.",
					"its use does not require the presence of advanced life support personnel.",
					"it delivers an unlimited number of shocks with the same amount of energy."
				],
				"question": "The AED is MOST advantageous to the EMT because:",
				"source": "See Cardiac Arrest"
			},
			"back": "it delivers prompt defibrillation to patients with ventricular fibrillation."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"a coronary artery is totally occluded by plaque.",
					"one or more coronary arteries suddenly spasm.",
					"myocardial oxygen demand exceeds supply.",
					"myocardial oxygen supply exceeds the demand."
				],
				"question": "Angina pectoris occurs when:",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "myocardial oxygen demand exceeds supply."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Nitroglycerin should be administered between the cheek and gum.",
					"Nitroglycerin usually relieves anginal chest pain within 5 minutes.",
					"The potency of nitroglycerin is increased when exposed to light.",
					"A maximum of five nitroglycerin doses should be given to a patient."
				],
				"question": "Which of the following statements regarding nitroglycerin is correct?",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care for Chest Pain or Discomfort"
			},
			"back": "Nitroglycerin usually relieves anginal chest pain within 5 minutes."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"are elderly.",
					"cannot afford it.",
					"are in denial.",
					"do not trust EMTs."
				],
				"question": "The MOST common reason that many people experiencing AMI do not seek immediate medical attention is because they:",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "are in denial."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"two",
					"five",
					"four",
					"three"
				],
				"question": "Most patients are instructed by their physician to take up to _______ doses of nitroglycerin before calling EMS.",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care for Chest Pain or Discomfort"
			},
			"back": "three"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"angina pectoris.",
					"arteriosclerosis.",
					"acute ischemia.",
					"atherosclerosis."
				],
				"question": "Narrowing of the coronary arteries caused by a buildup of fatty deposits is called:",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "atherosclerosis."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"contact medical control.",
					"assess for a pulse for 20 seconds.",
					"perform CPR for 30 seconds.",
					"dry the chest if it is wet."
				],
				"question": "Prior to attaching the AED to a cardiac arrest patient, the EMT should:",
				"source": "See Cardiac Arrest"
			},
			"back": "dry the chest if it is wet."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"femoral arteries.",
					"anterior tibial arteries.",
					"posterior tibial arteries.",
					"peroneal arteries."
				],
				"question": "The iliac arteries immediately subdivide into the:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "femoral arteries."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-17-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Pulmonary arteries",
					"Inferior vena cava",
					"Superior vena cava",
					"Pulmonary veins"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following blood vessels transports oxygenated blood?",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "Pulmonary veins"
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-17",
		"label": "Chapter 17"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}